marella.com 2015-10-17

# Privacy

**PRIVACY INFORMATION NOTICE**  
Thank you for providing us with your personal data.  
By visiting the website of Marella, marella.com you acknowledge and accept the procedures described in this Privacy Notice.  
The Marella brand is produced by Marella S.r.l. and marketed online via the website marella.com by E-volve Service Sagl.

**WHY THIS NOTICE**  
These pages describe the methods and purposes of the management of this website marella.com  concerning the processing of personal data of the users consulting the site and using its functions, as better described below, as well as current and potential consumers who may consent to the processing of their personal data notified to the stores distributing the products of the brand.  
This information notice is published also pursuant to art. 13 of Italian Legislative Decree (D.Lgs.) no. 196/2003 - Data Protection Act to anyone interacting with the  _web_  services of the website marella.com, which are accessible on-line, and anyone interacting with the stores distributing the products of the brand.  
This information notice also aims as far as possible to comply with Recommendation no. 2/2001 which the European authorities for data protection, within the Group established by art. 29 of Directive no. 95/46/EC, adopted on  May 17, 2001 to identify some minimum requirements for the gathering of personal data  _on-line_ , and, particularly, the methods, timing and nature of the information which the data controllers must provide users when they connect to the web page, whatever the purpose of such connection.

**METHODS AND PURPOSES OF THE DATA PROCESSING**  
Following the consultation of this website, information may be processed concerning identified or identifiable persons.  
It is explicitly declared that if the user has come to the web services of the website marella.com, which is managed by  Marella S.r.l., as a result of advertisements on other websites and/or social networks (Facebook, Google etc.), it is possible that such action may be subject to impersonal and anonymous statistical monitoring in order to control the functions of the advertisements, also for security purposes.  
It should be noted that this website marella.com from the Marella brand, which is managed by  Marella S.r.l., in the section destined for on-line sale of products and for all concerning the procedure of executing the purchase as requested by the user (art. 42 of the Data Protection Act i), web services are supplied by E-volve Service Sagl. to which the user data is notified at the same time and which processes the data in compliance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.  
It should also be noted that the data provided by the user may be communicated and used by individuals located outside the countries of the EU and that by agreeing to the use of the data as described in this notice you are giving your express authorisation for the transferal of your data, always in conformity to and with respect for the present Privacy Policy.  
Marella S.r.l. and the companies of the Max Mara Group or any third parties appointed there by to provide on-line services will share the data, using it in compliance with this Privacy Policy. These parties, as better identified hereafter, may analyse and process the aforementioned data in order to improve the products and services supplied.  
The personal data is processed using mainly electronic or on-line means.  
In the stores, the data may also be processed in hard copy and subsequently copied onto the computer platforms.  
As a rule, the personal data may be processed differently depending on the purposes for which the user has consented their gathering and use.  
In this regard, it is therefore possible to identify three different methods of gathering personal data, and consequently three different levels of processing, as specified below:

a) Newsletter  
The user registers his/her e-mail address exclusively in order to receive all updates and news (sales initiatives, competitions, prize draws, opening of new stores, promotional sales in-store and on-line, cultural events etc.) concerning the brand and all brands of the Max Mara Group.  
It is also possible that the data is processed, with the user's consent, to create profiles based on language preferences defined according to the country indicated in the user's website navigation. In this case the purpose is that of arranging for communications to be sent in the most appropriate way possible, in line with the needs and interests of the customer.

b) “Guest” user  
The personal data provided by the user is exclusively that required to complete the on-line purchase and manage/perform all phases of the sale, from order preparation to product delivery. In this field, therefore, the data is used and processed exclusively for notification to those parties that Marella S.r.l. has appointed to manage and complete the order, who may not however in turn use or process it for other purposes.  
In particular, data must be entered in order to proceed with on-line purchases, complete orders and relative activities, manage payments, including anti-fraud controls for credit/debit card payments.  
For on-line sales  Marella S.r.l. uses the services of E-volve Service Sagl., and therefore in this case the data provided during the purchasing process (name, surname, address, credit/debit card number, delivery address if different from the invoicing address) will be sent to the person in charge of the anti-fraud controls for E-volve Service Sagl., with registered office in Via Cantonale 2b, CH-6928 Manno, Switzerland, and will be processed by them solely for that purpose (please also refer to the section on "Data Controller”). In this field, the data may also be used with reference to technical or commercial requests, concerning the state of progress of the orders and general requests for information;   
Marella S.r.l. may also use other companies to perform activities concerning the completion of orders and the delivery of the purchased products. These suppliers will be provided exclusively with the data required to perform their own specific tasks. Marella S.r.l. guarantees that such parties may not use the data for other purposes, and that they are also obliged to process the personal data in compliance with this privacy information notice, and in compliance with statutory requirements.

c) Registered user  
Users may provide their personal data on-line on this website  marella.com  through specific data entry screens, or at stores, also using paper forms. The personal data of registered users will be used for the purposes of profiling and, where explicitly requested, to send Newsletters, notices concerning commercial initiatives and promotions, to send advertising materials and any other promotional or commercial initiative or events, both by e-mail and by post.  
The data, including that used for user profiling, may also be provided to shipping agencies, telephone companies, editorial companies, advertising agencies, companies specialized in marketing analyses and/or market research, services companies for the management of promotions, including competitions and/or prize draws, to other stores, also on-line, of the commercial chains belonging to the brands distributing the products of the Max Mara Group, consultants and agents, and to the suppliers of the purchased products.  
After log-in using their own credentials, registered users may also proceed to purchase the products on-line. In this case, the personal data will also be processed in order to complete the on-line transaction and manage and perform all related phases, from order preparation to product delivery. In this field, therefore, the data is used and processed for notification to those parties that  Marella S.r.l. has appointed to manage and complete the order, who may not however in turn use or process it for other purposes.  
In particular, the data must be processed during the on-line purchase to complete orders and relative activities, manage payments, including anti-fraud controls for credit/debit card payments. During the purchasing process, the data of registered users (name, surname, address, credit card number, delivery address if different from the invoicing address) will be sent to the person in charge of the anti-fraud controls for E-volve Service Sagl., with registered offices in Via Cantonale 2b, CH-6928 Manno, Switzerland, and will be processed by them solely for that purpose (please also refer to the section on "Data Controller”). In this field, the data may also be used with reference to technical or commercial requests, concerning the state of progress of the orders and general requests for information;  
Marella S.r.l. may also use other companies to perform activities concerning the completion of orders and the delivery of the purchased products.  These suppliers will be provided exclusively with the data required to perform their own specific tasks. Marella S.r.l. guarantees that such parties may not use the data for other purposes, and that they are also obliged to process the personal data in compliance with this privacy information notice, and in compliance with statutory requirements.  
In some cases it is possible that the user can be identified directly or indirectly in person.  
This is however done in compliance with the principle of strict necessity.   
The website is therefore structured in such a way that only the the minimum indispensable use of personal data is made.  
When the purposes pursued can be performed using data in anonymous form, this will be the privileged procedure, thus excluding that the person can be identified.  
Please also note that in some cases we may be required by law to disclose the data provided to third parties; in this case, your data may be made available to third parties who will process it autonomously and solely for the aforementioned purposes (for example, when requested by the police, the magistrates or other competent authorities).  
As far as permitted by the current state of technology, we have adopted and comply with security measures to prevent the loss, unlawful or improper use of, or unauthorized access to, your data.

**THE DATA CONTROLLER**  
It is important for users to be aware of the circumstance that, as this document aims to expressly inform, the recording through this website marella.com, or in any case the notification of your data in the above-described methods, will also be valid and effective for the companies of the Max Mara Group and those appointed by them to provide on-line sales services and who shall therefore share such information all comply with this Policy Privacy.  
Here below is the updated list as of the date of publication of this Policy of the companies in the Max Mara Group which may share the personal data gathered via this website as well as the data of the companies managing on-line product sales which are therefore co-controllers of the data:

Companies and references:  
**Max Mara S.r.l.**  
Via G. Maramotti 4 – 42124 Reggio Emilia - Italia  
Tel: +39 0522 3991,  Fax: +39 0522 399.3993

**Manifatture del Nord S.r.l.**  
Via Mazzacurati 6 – 42122 Reggio Emilia – Italia  
Tel: +39 0522 3581, Fax: +39 0522 550018

**Marella S.r.l.**  
Via  G. Maramotti 4  \- 42124 Reggio Emilia - Italia  
Tel: +39 0522 927411,  Fax: +39 0522 9274333

**Marina Rinaldi S.r.l.**  
Via Mazzacurati 4, - 42122 Reggio Emilia – Italia  
Tel: +39 0522 3591,  Fax: +39 0522 557701

**Diffusione Tessile S.r.l.**  
Via Santi, 8 - 42025 Corte Tegge Cavriago (RE) - Italia  
Tel: +39 0522 494953,  Fax: +39 0522 944385

**Max Mara Fashion Group S.r.l.**  
Via del Carmine, 10 - 10122 Torino – Italia  
Tel: +39 0522 3991, Fax: +39 0522 399.3254

The above-listed companies will autonomously process the data for the activities concerning their own brands and will share them with the other companies in the Max Mara Group (including those outside the EU) and/or with its online and offline distributors, exclusively for the purposes listed above (Methods and purposes of the data processing).

**TYPES OF DATA PROCESSED**  
_Navigation data_  
During normal operation, the computer systems and  _software_  procedures for the operation of this website acquire some personal data, including through the use of so-called cookies, which is implicitly transmitted in the use of Internet communication protocols.  
This information is not gathered in order to be associated to the identified persons, but which by its very nature could, if processed and associated to data held by third parties, lead to the identification of the users.  
This category of data includes the IP addresses or names of computer domains used by the users when connecting to the website,  _URI (Uniform Resource Identifier)_  addresses of requested resources, the time of the request, the method used in submitting the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in reply, the numerical code indicating the state of the reply given by the  _server_  (OK, error, etc.) and other parameters concerning the operating system and computer environment of the user.  
This data is used solely to gather statistical information on the use of the website and to check that it is working correctly.

**NON-MANDATORY NATURE OF THE PROVISION OF DATA**  
In addition to what stated for the navigation data, users are free to provide their personal data in the specific request forms.  
If they do not provide such information, however, it will not be possible to satisfy the requests made or continue with the procedures for which the personal data needs to be acquired.  
Specific security measures are ensured in order to prevent the loss of data, unlawful or improper use or unauthorised access.

**RIGHTS OF THE PARTIES CONCERNED**  
The parties to which the personal data refers have the right at any time to obtain the confirmation of the existence or otherwise of their data and to know the contents and origin thereof, check the exact nature, check the correctness or request the integration, updating or correction of their data (Article 7 of the Data Protection Act).  
Pursuant to the same article, they have the right to obtain the deletion, transformation into an anonymous form or suspension of any data processed in breach of the law, and to oppose the processing of their data for legitimate reasons.  
Requests should be sent by e-mail to: info@marella.com

**P3P**  
This Privacy Notice can be automatically consulted on the most recent  _browsers_  using the P3P standard (" _Platform for Privacy Preferences Project_ ") proposed by the  _World Wide Web Consortium_  (www.w3c.org).  
All efforts are made to ensure as far as possible the inter-operability of the functions of this website with the automatic control mechanisms applied for the purposes of privacy, available in some products used by the users.  
Considering that the present state of automatic control mechanisms does not currently ensure that they are free from errors or malfunctions, it is specified that this document, published on www.marella.com/privacy constitutes the " _Privacy Policy_ " of this website and those connected thereto, which will be subject to updating.  
For any further information, you are kindly invited to contact our Customer Service or send an e-mail to the following address: info@marella.com  
To know your rights and keep abreast of the privacy laws concerning the protection of persons in processing of personal data, you are advised to consult the website of the Ombudsman for the protection of personal data at http://www.garanteprivacy.it/.

**APPLICABLE LAW**  
This Privacy Policy is governed by Italian Law and in particular by the Data Protection Act (Italian Legislative Decree no. 196 of  June 30, 2003) which governs the processing of personal data - including data held abroad - by all parties with residence or headquarters in Italy.  
The Act ensures that personal data is processed with respect for fundamental rights and freedoms, and personal dignity, with particular reference to confidentiality, personal identity and the right to the protection of personal data.

**AMENDMENTS AND UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**  
Marella S.r.l. may amend or merely update, even partially, the Privacy Policy pertaining to its website, also in line with any amendments to the statutory laws or regulations governing this matter and protecting your rights.  
It is therefore important to frequently and regularly consult this section in order to check the publication of the most recent and updated version of the Privacy Policy.
